{
    "subject": "resource/Charles_Bukowski",
    "predicate": "ontology/nationality",
    "object": "resource/German_American",
    "human_readable": "The nationality of Charles Bukowski is German American.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9134822487831116,
            "question": "What nationality was Charles Bukowski?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8464449644088745,
            "question": "Was Charles Bukowski American?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4922620356082916,
            "question": "When was Charles Bukowski born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42424026131629944,
            "question": "What country did Charles Bukowski's heritage come from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39466872811317444,
            "question": "Are there other famous German Americans?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30049657821655273,
            "question": "What is meant by the term 'German American'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2795425355434418,
            "question": "Where did Charles Bukowski live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19526098668575287,
            "question": "Did Charles Bukowski have dual citizenship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16391311585903168,
            "question": "What type of writing is Charles Bukowski known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1018889993429184,
            "question": "What are some key themes in Charles Bukowski's works?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The nationality of Charles Bukowski is German American.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4049_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of writing is Charles Bukowski known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4049_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Charles Bukowski have dual citizenship?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4049_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Charles Bukowski live?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4049_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4049_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4049_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4049_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4049_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4049_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4049_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4049_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4049_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4049_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4049_74.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that Charles Bukowski was born in Germany to a German-American father but immigrated to the United States at a young age. He is described as an American poet, novelist, and short story writer, which supports the statement that his nationality is German American."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}